<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cyprus Public Opinion Trends</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cyprus Public Opinion Trends</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How disaffected are Cypriots with Political Institutions?: European Union Institutions</title>
      <link>/post/disaffection-with-eu-institutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/disaffection-with-eu-institutions/</guid>
      <description>The second part of the series examining the extent to which global trends in disaffection towards political institutions manifest themselves in Cyprus, focuses on European Union institutions. The analysis finds that trust in the EU and its institutions (European Parliament, European Commission, European Central Bank) fell among Cypriots from 2004 onward. However, this was mostly due to lower trust among Greek-Cypriots, as trust is higher and remained more stable for Turkish-Cypriots during this period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How disaffected are Cypriots with Political Institutions? : Political Parties</title>
      <link>/post/disaffection-with-parties/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/disaffection-with-parties/</guid>
      <description>This two part series examines the extent to which global trends in disaffection towards political institutions also manifest themselves in Cyprus and how it compares to other EU countries. Trust towards political parties is examined in this first part of the series. The analysis finds that trust in parties has been declining over the past 15 years, particularly from 2014 onwards. In contrast, the EU as a whole experienced relative stability during this period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to C-POT</title>
      <link>/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Cyprus Public Opinion Trends (C-POT)!
Through this blog I’ll be providing non-partisan information and quantitative analysis on Cypriots’ attitudes towards the social, political and cultural issues their society faces. Its objective is to make Cypriots’ views more accessible to the general public, journalists, academics and political professionals. Discussion of Greek-Cypriot and Turkish-Cypriot public opinion is a central feature of this endeavor. Quantitative analyses are based on publicly available survey data and to ensure transparency, information to replicate all analyses is provided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/about/</guid>
      <description>About
Welcome to Cyprus Public Opinion Trends (C-POT)!
The blog provides non-partisan information and quantitative analysis on Cypriots’ attitudes towards the social, political and cultural issues their society faces. Its objective is to make Cypriots’ views more accessible to the general public, journalists, academics and political professionals. Discussion of Greek-Cypriot and Turkish-Cypriot public opinion is a central feature of this endeavor. Quantitative analyses are based on publicly available survey data and to ensure transparency software code to replicate all analyses is provided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact</title>
      <link>/top/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact
Please feel free to send me comments, suggestions, and ideas at: yioryos@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>replication</title>
      <link>/top/replication/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/replication/</guid>
      <description>This site was created using Markdown in the R statistical software, with the Blogdown package and a Hugo
theme. Analyses were conducted in R and visualizations use the plotly package.
R Markdown files with replication information for all analyses can be found on my GitHub page in the ‘post’ folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>replication</title>
      <link>/top/replication/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/replication/</guid>
      <description>Replication Information
This site is created in the R statistical program using Markdown with the blogdown package and a Hugo theme. Analyses are conducted in R, and visualizations are created using the plotly package.
R Markdown files with replication scripts and data sources for all analyses can be found on my GitHub page in the “post” folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>subscribe</title>
      <link>/top/subscribe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/subscribe/</guid>
      <description> Loading…  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>