<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cyprus Public Opinion Trends</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cyprus Public Opinion Trends</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Perceptions Towards Corruption and Accountability in the Public Sector</title>
      <link>/post/perceptions-towards-corruption/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/perceptions-towards-corruption/</guid>
      <description>Corruption and conflict of interest among government officials is at the forefront of public discourse in Cyprus due to recent scandals. This post examines Cypriots’ perceptions towards public sector corruption and accountability.
• The vast majority of Cypriots feel that corruption among the civil service, state officials, and business executives is pervasive. Greek-Cypriots in particular overwhelmingly express that corruption is prevalent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cypriots’ Views on the Role of Religion in Public Life</title>
      <link>/post/cypriots-views-on-religions-role-in-public-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cypriots-views-on-religions-role-in-public-life/</guid>
      <description>After examining religiosity in Cyprus, we now turn to people’s views on the role of religion in politics and public affairs.
• There is widespread belief in the separation of religion and government across both communities. However, non-trivial support for religious reasoning in public affairs also exists.
• The vast majority of Cypriots are clear in their conviction that religious leaders should not influence political decision-making and electoral processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religiosity in Cyprus</title>
      <link>/post/religiosity-in-cyprus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/religiosity-in-cyprus/</guid>
      <description>How important is religion in Cypriots’ lives in light of global trends in religiosity?
• Religious values are prevalent in Cyprus and entrenched in people’s identity, regardless of whether one practices or considers themselves to be religious.
• Nearly all Cypriots consider themselves to be part of a religion or religious denomination, irrespective of whether they attend religious services.
• Overall, Greek-Cypriots tend to be slightly more religious than Turkish-Cypriots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideological Identification in Cyprus</title>
      <link>/post/ideological-identification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ideological-identification/</guid>
      <description>How do Cypriots classify their political ideologies and preferences? To what extent do they identify with the notions of the “left” and “right”?
• In general, Turkish-Cypriots are more likely to identify with the left or right than Greek-Cypriots. In turn, Greek-Cypriots are more likely to identify with the centre or to not express a preference than Turkish-Cypriots.
• The proportion of Cypriots that do not express a preference has gone from being the least common to the most common preference between 2004-2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Disaffected are Cypriots with Political Institutions?: European Union Institutions</title>
      <link>/post/disaffection-with-eu-institutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/disaffection-with-eu-institutions/</guid>
      <description>The second part of the series examining the extent to which global trends in disaffection towards political institutions manifest themselves in Cyprus, focuses on European Union institutions. The analysis finds that trust in the EU and its institutions (European Parliament, European Commission, European Central Bank) fell among Cypriots from 2011 onward. However, this is mostly due to lower trust among Greek-Cypriots, as trust is higher and remained more stable for Turkish-Cypriots during this period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Disaffected are Cypriots with Political Institutions? : Political Parties</title>
      <link>/post/disaffection-with-parties/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/disaffection-with-parties/</guid>
      <description>This two part series examines the extent to which global trends in disaffection towards political institutions also manifest themselves in Cyprus and how it compares to other EU countries. Trust towards political parties is examined in this first part of the series. The analysis finds that trust in parties has been declining over the past 15 years, particularly from 2014 onwards. In contrast, the EU as a whole experienced relative stability during this period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to C-POT</title>
      <link>/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Cyprus Public Opinion Trends (C-POT)!
Through this blog I’ll be providing non-partisan information and quantitative analysis on Cypriots’ attitudes towards the social, political and cultural issues their society faces. Its objective is to make Cypriots’ views more accessible to the general public, journalists, academics and political professionals. Discussion of Greek-Cypriot and Turkish-Cypriot public opinion is a central feature of this endeavor. Quantitative analyses are based on publicly available survey data, and to ensure transparency information to replicate all analyses is provided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/about/</guid>
      <description>About
Welcome to Cyprus Public Opinion Trends (C-POT)!
The blog provides non-partisan information and quantitative analysis on Cypriots’ attitudes towards the social, political and cultural issues their society faces. Its objective is to make Cypriots’ views more accessible to the general public, journalists, academics and political professionals. Discussion of Greek-Cypriot and Turkish-Cypriot public opinion is a central feature of this endeavor. Quantitative analyses are based on publicly available survey data, and to ensure transparency software code to replicate all analyses is provided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact</title>
      <link>/top/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contact
Please feel free to send me comments, suggestions, and ideas at: yioryos@gmail.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>replication</title>
      <link>/top/replication/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/replication/</guid>
      <description>This site was created using Markdown in the R statistical software, with the Blogdown package and a Hugo
theme. Analyses were conducted in R and visualizations use the plotly package.
R Markdown files with replication information for all analyses can be found on my GitHub page in the ‘post’ folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>replication</title>
      <link>/top/replication/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/replication/</guid>
      <description>Replication Information
This site is created in the R statistical program using Markdown with the blogdown package and a Hugo theme. Analyses are conducted in R, and visualizations are created using the plotly package.
R Markdown files with replication scripts and data sources for all analyses can be found on my GitHub page in the “post” folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>subscribe</title>
      <link>/top/subscribe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/top/subscribe/</guid>
      <description> Loading…  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>