<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>religion on Cyprus Public Opinion Trends</title>
    <link>/tags/religion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in religion on Cyprus Public Opinion Trends</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/religion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cypriots’ Views on the Role of Religion in Public Life</title>
      <link>/post/cypriots-views-on-religions-role-in-public-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cypriots-views-on-religions-role-in-public-life/</guid>
      <description>After examining religiosity in Cyprus, we now turn to people’s views on the role of religion in politics and public affairs.
• There is widespread belief in the separation of religion and government across both communities. However, non-trivial support for religious reasoning in public affairs also exists.
• The vast majority of Cypriots are clear in their conviction that religious leaders should not influence political decision-making and electoral processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Religiosity in Cyprus</title>
      <link>/post/religiosity-in-cyprus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/religiosity-in-cyprus/</guid>
      <description>How important is religion in Cypriots’ lives in light of global trends in religiosity?
• Religious values are prevalent in Cyprus and entrenched in people’s identity, regardless of whether one practices or considers themselves to be religious.
• Nearly all Cypriots consider themselves to be part of a religion or religious denomination, irrespective of whether they attend religious services.
• Overall, Greek-Cypriots tend to be slightly more religious than Turkish-Cypriots.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>